Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.inventory4 Mss.B.B61.inventory04
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents D
  - Dixon, Roland B. (Box 22)
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Feb. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Apr. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Nov. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Dec. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Dec. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Apr. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1924 Feb. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1924 Mar. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1924 Mar. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1924 Mar. 11; 2p
    - From Boas, 1924 Mar. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1924 Mar. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1924 Mar. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1924 Mar. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1924 Mar. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1924 Mar. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1924 Mar. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 Feb. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 Feb. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Sep. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Oct. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Nov. 17; 2p
    - From Boas, 1928 Nov. 23; 2p
    - From Boas, 1928 Dec. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Feb. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Mar. 21; 2p
    - From Boas, 1929 May 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 June 5; 2p
    - From Boas, 1930 June 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 22; 1p
      - also June 10 & Nov. 18'31, 1931 May 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1898 Jan. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1899 Feb. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1899 June 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1900 Feb. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1900 Mar. 31; 2p
    - To Boas, 1905 Jan. 12
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 27
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 17
    - To Boas, 1906 June 2
    - To Boas, 1906 June 10
    - To Boas, 1906 July 18
    - To Boas, 1906 Sep. 25
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 23
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 23
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 31
    - To Boas, 1907 Feb. 15
    - To Boas, 1907 May 23
    - To Boas, 1907 Sep. 21
    - To Boas, 1907 Sep. 25
    - To Boas, 1907 Sep. 30
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 7
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 9
    - To Boas, 1907 Nov. 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 1
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 10
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 16
    - To Boas, 1908 Feb. 13
    - To Boas, 1908 Mar. 7; 2p
    - To Boas, 1908 Apr. 5
    - To Boas, 1908 June 12
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 1
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 10
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 13
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 25
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 4
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 9
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 16
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 19
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 22
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 1
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 5
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 14
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 18
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 21
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 2
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 5
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 13
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 23
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 4
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 10
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 14
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 21
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 27
    - To Boas, 1909 May 1
    - To Boas, 1909 May 8
    - To Boas, 1909 May 13
    - To Boas, 1909 May 19
    - To Boas, 1909 June 4
    - To Boas, 1910 Sep. 18
    - To Boas, 1910 Nov. 14
    - To Boas, 1910 Nov. 17
    - To Boas, 1910 Dec. 8
    - To Boas, 1910 Dec. 9
    - To Boas, 1910 Dec. 21
    - To Boas, 1911 Jan. 9
    - To Boas, 1911 Jan. 18; 3p
    - To Boas, 1911 Feb. 1; 2p
    - To Boas, 1911 Feb. 24; 2p
    - To Boas, 1911 May 7
    - To Boas, 1911 May 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1911 Sep. 21
    - To Boas, 1911 Sep. 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 1
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1912 Feb. 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1912 Feb. 12
    - To Boas, 1912 Feb. 29
    - To Boas, 1912 Mar. 12
    - To Boas, 1912 Apr. 23
    - To Boas, 1912 May 6; 2p
    - To Boas, 1912 May 13; 2p
    - To Boas, 1912 May 14
    - To Boas, 1912 June 6
    - To Boas, 1912 Sep. 4
    - To Boas, 1913 July 1; 4p
    - To Boas, 1913 Sep. 2
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 2; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 6
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 7
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 17
    - To Boas, 1914 Jan. 2
    - To Boas, 1914 Jan. 5
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 5
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 10
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 12
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 21
    - To Boas, 1914 May 26
    - To Boas, 1914 Sep 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1914 Oct. 7
    - To Boas, 1914 Oct. 19
    - To Boas, 1914 Oct. 29
    - To Boas, 1914 Nov. 4
    - To Boas, 1914 Nov. 6
    - To Boas, 1914 Dec. 2
    - To Boas, 1914 Dec. 8
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 7
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 28
    - To Boas, 1915 Apr. 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1915 May 10
    - To Boas, 1916 Sep. 30
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 8
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 31
    - To Boas, 1917 Jun 14
    - To Boas, 1917 Jun 23
    - To Boas, 1917 Sep. 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1917 Dec. 28
    - To Boas, 1918 Jan. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Dec. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Sep. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Feb. 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1921 Apr. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Nov. 22; 2p
    - To Boas, 1921 Dec. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Dec. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Dec. 24; 2p
    - To Boas, 1922 Oct. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1922 Oct. 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 21; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 1; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 Apr. 5; 2p
    - To Boas, 1924 Feb. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Feb. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Feb. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Mar. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Mar. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Mar. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1924 Mar. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Mar. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Mar. 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1924 Mar. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Mar. 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1924 Apr. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Feb. 3; 2p
    - To Boas, 1925 Feb. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 May 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Dec. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Sep. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 29; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 Sep. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 June 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 29; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Mar. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Mar. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Apr. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 May 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 May 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 June 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 June 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 May 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 May 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 June 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Sep. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 12; 1p
    - To RBD from Guthrie, W.D., 1924 Mar. 21
    - To RBD from Lowell, A.L., 1910 Dec. 17
    - To RBD from Phillips, W., 1913 Dec. 22
    - To RBD from S., H.T., 1909 Apr. 2
  - Dobroscke., W. (Box 22)
    - 1913 Oct. 31
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 15; 1p
    - also see FB to Engerrand, 1913 Oct. 31
  - Dodd, Bella V. (Box 22)
    - From Boas, 1940 July 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 July?; 1p
  - Dodd, Wm. E. (Box 22)
    - From Boas, 1938 Mar. 18; 1p
      - also see open letter, re Spain, replies, 1938 Jan.
    - To Boas, 1938 July 10; 1p
    - To Burlingham, C.C., 1939 Feb. 3; 1p
    - To Fackenthal, F.D., 1935 Apr. 21; 1p
  - Dodd, Mead, & Co. (Box 22)
    - From Boas, 1905 Apr. 29
  - Dodds, Elizabeth (Box 22)
    - To Boas, 1906 Dec. 6; 1p
  - Dodds, H.W. (Box 22)
    - From Boas, 1935 Feb. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Oct. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 May 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Dec. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Feb. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Oct. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 June 1; 1p
  - Dodge (Box 22)
    - From Boas, 1906 Apr. 18
  - Dodge, Alice L. (Box 22)
    - From Boas, 1940 Aug. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Sep. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 July 30; 1p
  - Dodge, H.L. (Box 22)
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 8; 2p
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 6; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 27; 1p
  - Dodge, M.H. (Box 22)
    - To Boas, 1925 Mar. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Mar. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Apr. 6; 1p
  - Dodge, R. (Box 22)
    - see FB to Woodworth, R.S., 1931 Sep. 2
  - Dodge, Richard E. (Box 22)
    - From Boas, 1912 Dec. 4
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 5
  - Dodge, R.E.? (Box 22)
    - To Boas, 1931 Jan. 4; 1p
  - Doepenksha, H. -- to FB, 1928 Dec. 7; 1p (Box 22)
  - Doerflinger, Wm. M. (Box 22)
    - To Boas, 1938 July 29; 1p
  - Doerschuk, B. (Box 22)
    - From Boas, 1934 Mar. 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1934 Apr. 4; 1p
  - Doke, C.M. (Box 22)
    - From Boas, 1925 Jan. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 May 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Aug. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Feb. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 17; 1p
    - To Parsons, E., 1924 Dec. 19
    - To Jones, T.J., 1924 Oct. 22; 2p
    - To Boas, 1925 Mar. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Apr. 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1925 Mar. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Sep. 20; 1p
  - Dollard, Charles (Box 22)
    - From Boas, 1938 Mar. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Feb. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Mar. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Mar. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Oct. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Feb. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Jan. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 June 11; 1p
  - Doly, R.S. -- to FB, 1917 Mar. 15 (Box 22)
  - Domine, R. (Box 22)
    - To Boas, 1888 June 14; 3p
  - Donaldson, Henry H. (Box 22)
    - From Boas, 1905 Jan. 14
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 16
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 14
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 13
    - From Boas, 1909 mar. 22
    - From Boas, 1914 Oct. 24; 2p
    - From Boas, 1914 Dec. 9
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 13
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 17; [19?]
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 22
    - From Boas, 1917 Oct. 12
    - From Boas, 1918 Jan. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Apr. 9; 2p
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 18; 2p
    - From Boas, 1920 Jan. 29; 2p
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1922 Nov. 23; 1p
      - Jan. 2/23 with, 1922 Dec. 5; 1p
        - HHD's reply on back, 1922 Dec. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Apr. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Apr. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 Apr. 23; 2p
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Apr. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 May 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Mar. 14; 2p
    - From Boas, 1935 Mar. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1893 Jan. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1893 Sep. 7; 2p
    - To Boas, 1893 Dec. 22; 2p
    - To Boas, 1893 Dec. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1894 Jan. 10
    - To Boas, 1894 Jan. 24
    - To Boas, 1894 Mar. 6
    - To Boas, 1894 Apr. 25
    - To Boas, 1894 May 20
    - To Boas, 1894 May 26
    - To Boas, 1894 June 14
    - To Boas, 1894 June 18
    - To Boas, 1894 June 25
    - To Boas, 1894 June 30
    - To Boas, 1894 July 13
    - To Boas, 1894 July 27
    - To Boas, 1894 July 28
    - To Boas, 1894 Aug. 6
    - To Boas, 1894 Aug. 10
    - To Boas, 1894 Aug. 18
    - To Boas, 1894 Sep. 7
    - To Boas, 1894 Sep. 18
    - To Boas, 1894 Sep. 21
    - To Boas, 1894 Sep. 24
    - To Boas, 1894 Oct. 1
    - To Boas, 1894 Oct. 5
    - To Boas, 1894 Dec. 29
    - To Boas, 1895 Feb. 4
    - To Boas, 1895 Feb. 27
    - To Boas, 1895 Apr. 22
    - To Boas, 1895 May 4
    - To Boas, 1895 May 13
    - To Boas, 1895 May 14
    - To Boas, 1895 July 5
    - To Boas, 1895 Oct. 22
    - To Boas, 1895 Nov. 5
    - To Boas, 1895 Jan. 2, 1896 Jan. 18
    - To Boas, 1896 May 20
    - To Boas, 1896 May?
    - To Boas, 1896 Aug. 16
    - To Boas, 1896 Nov. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1897 Dec. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1898 May 15
    - To Boas, 1898 May 23
    - To Boas, 1898 May 24
    - To Boas, 1898 June 13
    - To Boas, 1898 June 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1898 June 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1898 Aug. 10; 3p
    - To Boas, 1898 Aug. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1898 Oct. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1898 Dec. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1898 Dec. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1899 Feb. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1899 Feb. 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1899 Feb. 19
    - To Boas, 1899 Apr. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1899 June 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1899 Sep. 17; 3p
    - To Boas, 1900 Feb. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1900 July 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1902 Jan. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1902 July 19; 2p
    - To Boas, 1902 July 27; 4p
    - To Boas, 1903 Feb. 19; 2p
    - To Boas, 1903 June 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1903 Oct. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1904 Jan. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1904 Jan. 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1904 Feb. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1904 Nov. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1904 Nov. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1905 May 25
    - To Boas, 1905 June 28
    - To Boas, 1905 July 9
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 14
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 18
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 19
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 20
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 19
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 21
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 16
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 23
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 7
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 9
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 24
    - To Boas, 1914 Apr. 23
    - To Boas, 1914 Dec. 14
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 18
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 21
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 24
    - To Boas, 1915 Nov. 30
    - To Boas, 1916 Nov. 4 1916 Dec. 18
    - To Boas, 1917 Oct. 13
    - To Boas, 1918 Jan. 15; 2p
    - To Boas, 1919 Apr. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Nov. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Dec. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Dec. 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 Feb. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1922 Dec. 4; 1p
    - reverse of Dec. 22 letter from FB, 1923 Jan. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Apr. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Apr. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 May 4; 3p
    - To Boas, 1928 Dec. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Jan. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Jan. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Feb. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Apr. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 May 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Mar. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 3; 1p
    - HHD -- to Mrs. Krackowizer, 1895 May 20
  - Donaldson, Norman (Box 22)
    - From Boas, 1933 Feb. 13; 1p
  - Donner, O.W. (Box 22)
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 9; 1p
  - Donohue, E.K. (Box 22)
    - see Lindeman, E.O., 1936 June 26
  - Donohugh, A.C.L. (Box 22)
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Apr. 16; 7p
  - Dooley, Parker (Box 22)
    - From Boas, 1934 Apr. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 May 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Apr. 9; 1p
  - Dopsch -- (Akadem. Senat der U. Wien) (Box 22)
    - To Boas, 1921 July 14; 1p
  - Doremus, Secour & Seaman (Box 22)
    - June 2, 2p
    - From Boas, 1910 June 6
  - Dorfman, J. (Box 22)
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 12; 1p
  - Dormathy [?], W.J. (Box 22)
    - To Boas, 1887 May 17
  - Dorman, N.H. (Box 22)
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 5
    - To Boas, 1913 Nov. 3; 1p
  - Dornfeldt, Walter (Box 22)
    - From Boas, 1932 Jan. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Jan. 12; 1p
  - Dorrance, F. (Box 22)
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 6; 1p
  - Dorsey, E.A. (Box 22)
    - To Boas, 1912 Oct. 28
    - To Boas, 1913 Sep. 13
  - Dorsey, George A. (Box 22)
    - From Boas, 1894 Feb. 1
    - From Boas, 1896 Sep. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1900 Nov. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1900 Dec. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1901 Feb. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1901 Mar. 2
    - From Boas, 1902 Jan. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1902 Feb. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1902 May 2
    - From Boas, 1902 May 15
    - From Boas, 1904 Feb. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 28
    - From Boas, 1906 Mar. 7
    - From Boas, 1906 Sep. 18
    - From Boas, 1906 Sep. 24
    - From Boas, 1906 Oct. 2
    - From Boas, 1906 Nov. 23
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 29
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 3
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 24
    - From Boas, 1907 May 21; 2p
    - From Boas, 1907 May 27
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 12
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 16
    - From Boas, 1907 Dec. 16 & Nov. 15; 2p
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 8
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 15; 2p
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 31
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 19; 3p
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 26
    - From Boas, 1909 May 5; 2p
    - From Boas, 1909 May 26
    - From Boas, 1909 July 3; 4p
    - From Boas, 1909 July 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1909 Aug. 17
    - From Boas, 1909 Aug. 17
    - From Boas, 1909 Sep. 20
    - From Boas, 1909 Oct. 27; 2p
    - From Boas, 1909 Oct. 30; 2p
    - From Boas, 1910 Apr. 25
    - From Boas, 1912 Nov. 1
    - From Boas, 1912 Nov. 20
    - From Boas, 1912 Nov. 22
    - From Boas, 1912 Nov. 25
    - From Boas, 1913 July 8 - 1912 Nov. 25
    - From Boas, 1928 Nov. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Dec. 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1896 June 19
    - To Boas, 1896 July 1
    - To Boas, 1896 Aug. 15
    - To Boas, 1896 Sep. 8
    - To Boas, 1896 Sep. 9
    - To Boas, 1901 Feb. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1902 Jan. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1902 Mar. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1902 Mar. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1902 Apr. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1902 Apr. 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1902 May 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1902 Sep. 15, 1902 June 16; 3p
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 22
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 2
    - To Boas, 1906 Sep. 6
    - To Boas, 1906 Sep. 24
    - To Boas, 1906 Oct. 3
    - To Boas, 1906 Oct. 9
    - To Boas, 1906 Nov. 13
    - To Boas, 1906 Nov. 19
    - To Boas, 1906 Dec. 1
    - To Boas, 1907 Mar. 26
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 1
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 19
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 22, Apr. 29
    - To Boas, 1907 May 1
    - To Boas, 1907 May 23
    - To Boas, 1907 May 23
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 15
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 24
    - To Boas, 1907 Nov. 29
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 21
    - To Boas, 1909 May 8, 1909 Mar. 27
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 2
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 12
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 28
    - To Boas, 1909 May 24
    - To Boas, 1909 July 25; 5p
    - To Boas, 1909 Oct.?; 2p
    - To Boas, 1909 Nov. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1909 Dec. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1912 Oct. 29
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 20
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 July 30
    - To Boas, 1928 Aug. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 24; 1p
    - GAD -- to Walcott, C.D., 1909 July 25; 1p
  - Dorsey, Mrs. George A. (Susan) (Box 22)
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 14; 1p
  - Dorsey, H.W. (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1927 May 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 June 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Aug. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Aug. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 June 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 June 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Sep. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 29; 1p
    - HWD -- to Trachtenberg, 1917 Nov. 8
  - Dorsey, J.O. (Box 23)
    - To Boas, 1887 Apr. 8
    - To Boas, 1888 Mar. 14
    - To Boas, 1888 Mar. 23
  - Dorsey, Marian B. (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1917 Feb. 7; 2p
    - To Boas, 1917 Feb. 5
  - Dorsey, Susan -- (see Mrs. Geo. A. above) (Box 22)
  - Dorzy (Box 23)
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 20; 1p
  - Dos Passos, J. (Box 23)
    - To Boas, 1933 Feb. 27
      - co-signers: FB
      - Frank, W.
      - Steffens, L.
      - see FB to Walsh, T.J., 1933 Feb. 27
      - co-signed by above
      - see FB to Curtis, C., 1933 Feb. 27
        see FB to Garner, J.N.
  - Doty, K.S. (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 17
  - Doubleday, Page & Co. (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 24
  - Douglas, Alice M. (Box 23)
    - To Boas, 1899 June 1
  - Douglas, F.H. (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1936 Feb. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Jan. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Mar. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 Dec. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Dec. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Feb. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 Nov. 28; 1p
  - Douglas, J. -- from FB, 1916 Dec. 9; 2p (Box 23)
  - Douglass, Ellwood (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1936 Aug. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Dec. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 July 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Dec. 2; 1p
  - Douglass, J. (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Apr. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 24; 1p
  - Dowell, C.W. (Box 23)
    - To Boas, 1903 Nov. 10; 1p
  - Downer, C.A. (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1916 Nov. 29; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1916 Nov. 29
    - From Boas, 1916 Dec. 2
    - From Boas, 1916 Dec. 2
    - To Boas, 1916 Nov. 30; 2p
  - Downes, Olin (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1940 Dec. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 16; 1p
  - Downey, H. (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1933 Apr. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Apr. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 June 21; 1p
  - Downs, M. (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1920 May 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1916 July 31
    - To Boas, 1917 June 27
    - To Boas, 1917 Aug. 30
    - To Boas, 1917 Oct. 1
    - To Boas, 1920 May 17; 4p
    - MD -- to Tozzer, 1916 June 12
  - Downs, Robert B. (Box 23)
    - see FB open letter, Spain, replies, 1938 Jan.
  - Doyle (Box 23)
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 25
  - Drahms, A. (Box 23)
    - To Boas, 1899 Nov. 15; 1p
  - Draper, H. (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 20
  - Drechler, D. (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1928 Mar. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Mar. 27; 1p
  - Dreiser, Theodore (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 May 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 May 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 May; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 31; 1p
    - see Amer. Comm. for World Cong. Against War, 1932 May 27
  - Drevermann, F.E. (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Dec. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Apr. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 22; 1p
  - Drews, Robert S. (Box 23)
    - To Boas, 1939 Dec. 18; 1p
  - Dreyer, E.R. (Box 23)
    - To Boas, 1910 Feb. 1
  - Dreyfus, C. (Box 23)
    - From Wallerstein, Leo, 1933 Oct. 18
  - Dreyfus, E.H. (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 27
  - Droege, A. Karl (Box 23)
    - To Boas, 1929 June 15; 4p
    - To Boas, 1929 June 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Aug. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Apr. 20; 4p
    - To Boas, 1930 Aug. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Apr. 21; 4p
    - To Boas, 1936 July 9; 4p
    - To Boas, 1936 Aug. 16; 4p
    - To Boas, 1939 Aug. 10; 6p
  - Drolsum, A.C. (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1924 Sep. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1924 Sep. 10; 3p
  - Dropsie College (Box 23)
    see Adler, Cyrus
  - Drucker, M.H. (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 22; 1p
    - To Michelson, N., 1931 Apr. 29; 1p
  - Drugelinsche Druckerei (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 21; 2p
  - Drugulin, W. (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1920 July 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Dec. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 June 30; 1p
  - Drum, W.N. (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1918 Jan. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 7
    - To Boas, 1918 Jan. 23 & Mar. 5
  - Drury, B. -- to Boas, 1935 Aug. 9 (Box 23)
  - Drury, J.W. (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1942 Sep. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1942 Sep. 24; 1p
  - Drygalski, Erich von (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1906 Aug. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1890 July 12; 4p
    - To Boas, 1906 Sep. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1890 Nov. 1; 4p
  - Dublin, B. (Box 23)
    - To Boas, 1931 May 11; 2p
  - Dublin, Louis I. (Box 23)
    - From Boas, 1903 June 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 11; 3p
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 28; 2p
    - From Boas, 1919 Nov. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Nov. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 May 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 May 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Nov. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Apr. 8; 2p
    - From Boas, 1930 Oct. 13; 1p